http://www.maritimenz.govt.nz/privacy.asp

Safety management systems
Maritime Operator Safety System (MOSS)
Safe Operational Plans (SOP)show subtopics for safe operational plans
Specified limits permit
International Safety Management Code (SOLAS)
Safety Case
Adventure activity operations
Maritime Labour Conventionshow subtopics for maritime labour convention
Pilotage
Pilotage Exemption Certificate (PEC)
Operating limits
Maritime Labour Conventionshow subtopics for maritime labour convention
Refunds or waivers of levies
Information for:  Seafarers Owner operators Multi-vessel Ports & Harbours Surveyors
Legislation, regulations and conventions
Oil and gas explorationshow subtopics for oil and gas exploration
Role of each agency
Exploration and production stagesshow subtopics for exploration and production stages
Responding to spillsshow subtopics for responding to spills
Marine Pollution Response Services (MPRS)
Response process and methods
Response equipment
Dispersantsshow subtopics for dispersants
NZOSCAs
Spill response case studiesshow subtopics for spill case studies
Maritime incident response
Rescue Coordination Centre (RCCNZ)
Marine Pollution Response Services (MPRS)
New Zealand Safer Boating Forum
New Zealand Maritime Forum (NZMF)
Our fundingshow subtopics for our funding
Maritime Levy
Oil Pollution Levy (OPL)
Auckland
Marine Pollution Response Service (MPRS)
Tauranga
New Plymouth
Napier
Wellington
Rescue Coordination Centre (RCCNZ)
Auckland
Marine Pollution Response Service (MPRS)
Tauranga
New Plymouth
Napier
Wellington (central office)
Rescue Coordination Centre New Zealand (RCCNZ)
Privacy
This privacy statement applies to all personal information held by Maritime New Zealand. The collection, storage, use and disclosure of personal information by Maritime New Zealand is subject to the Privacy Act.
Collection, storage and use of personal information by Maritime New Zealand
To perform its roles and functions under the Maritime Transport Act, Health and Safety at Work Act, Ship Registration Act and Maritime Security Act, Maritime New Zealand is required at times to collect and use personal information.
In accordance with the Privacy Act, Maritime New Zealand will collect personal information directly from the individual the information is about whenever possible. There may be times when Maritime New Zealand is permitted by the Privacy Act to collect personal information from third parties. Maritime New Zealand may also collect personal information that is publicly available.
Maritime New Zealand only collects personal information when it is necessary to achieve its lawful functions. Personal information is only used for purposes consistent with the reasons it was collected.
Maritime New Zealand has reasonable safeguards to protect personal information against loss and unauthorised access, use, modification, or disclosure.
See also:
Maritime NZ’s Transparency Statement
Disclosure of personal information by Maritime New Zealand
Maritime New Zealand only discloses personal information to third parties when authorised by the individual or permitted by the Privacy Act 1993 or otherwise required or permitted by law.
Accessing personal information
You have the right to request access to personal information about you held by Maritime New Zealand under the Privacy Act.
You also have the right to request correction of any personal information held about you by Maritime New Zealand. Maritime New Zealand will take reasonable steps to correct that information and to ensure that the information we hold is correct.
If you wish to access or correct personal information Maritime New Zealand holds about you, please contact:
The Privacy Officer
Maritime New Zealand
PO Box 25620
Wellington 6140
or by phone on +64 4 473 0111.
Other information
For further information on the Privacy Act 1993 please see the Privacy Commissioner’s website.
Privacy Commissioner[Privacy Commissioner website]
